gyach.com 2012-05-13

# Gyach SB | privacy

## Pricacy Policy Statement

Privacy Policy for **www.gyach.com** which is also referred as **Gyach SB** or **Gyach Social Bookmarking:It here to share** or **gyach.com**. If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at support[at]gyach.com

Warning: Any of your submission or view which you have posted on GyachSB in this public Social Bookmarking Site will become public domain. Your text will be available to anyone with an internet connection.

At www.gyach.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.gyach.com and how it is used. 

  1. **Personal Information**  
We provide many services which do not require any sort of registration or need of personal information, however to provide you more personalized experience as well as more sets of services we may ask you for registration or join our services through which we may collect following informations.
  2. **Information provided to us**  
During signup to **GyachSB** we may ask you for certain personal information like your interestes, your location, your Date of birth, your email addresss etc, all those information is taken only to provide you more presonalized environment and that information is available in your profile. You can always decide what information should made available to publicibly and what not. For certain information we also provide flexibility to provide us or not to provide us. 
  3. **GyachSB Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.gyach.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. Those information gathered are mostly standard in general and it is common practice by most of the website on the internet.  
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
  4. **Third Party Cookies and Web Beacons**  
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense, Kontera. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.gyach.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. www.gyach.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.  
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites

However for google if you would like to get more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

  5. **Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.gyach.com makes use of log files. We store standard information which is necessary for proper functioning of a website. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track userâs movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.  
We use Google Analytics service. You can find their privacy policy [here](http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy.html) .You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.gyach.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 
  6. **Information Security and Data Integrity**  
We, at **GyachSB** make sure that data with is us secured and we take various security measures to avoid / stop unauthorized access access to data. Only authorized GyachSB employees are allowed access data. We also make sure that whatsoever information is collected from , is collected for the indented use only and is used for the intended purpose only.
  7. **Information Sharing and Enforcement  
**We do not share or sell our members / users information with third party which do not compliance with this privacy policy until it does not fall in following circumstances.. 
    * If there is any legal intervention by govening body of the particular region for the purpose of investigation etc.
    * If there is need to enforce certain terms as per policy
    * If there is any new colleboration or relation being developed with GyachSB and other new organization then we shall contact you regarding your consent for further enhancing our services by sharing or providing merger of data to new collaboration.
    * If we have your consent to share your information
If you wish to contact us for the concern of dealing privacy policy or personal data then you can contact us at support[at]gyach.com. Its our policy to contact the concerned person regarding the issue as well as we will also cooperate as per rules local authority and governing body.
  8. **Updates in this Policy  
**We "GyachSB" or gyach.com or www.gyach.com reserves full right to modify, update this privacy policy at any time. Its your / user's responsibility to regularly check and the privacy policy. However if there is any big / major change then we will provide information by suitable means to the user about the changes in policy. Still if you have any concern regarding the working of policy then you can contact us at support[at]gyach.com
